<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>module</type>
		<description>Language labels for extension 'mathematicians'</description>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="pi1_title">mathematicians</label>
			<label index="pi1_ow-intro">
				This collection of the Mathematisches Forschungsinstitut Oberwolfach contains
				photographs of mathematicians from all over the world. The collection is based
				on a donation from Prof. Konrad Jacobs (Erlangen) in the 1950's and has been
				continued by taking photos from every single group visiting Oberwolfach since
				about 1998.
			</label>
			<label index="pi1_gen-intro">The intent of this project is to compile information about all the
				mathematicians of the world. For each individual they plan to show: name of
				the degree recipient, name of the university which awarded the (doctoral)
				degree, year, title of dissertation and name(s) of the advisor(s).
			</label>
			<label index="pi_search-hint">
				<![CDATA[<b>Searching</b>: All searches are truncated at the beginning and at the end (i.e. partial matches will work as well). For example: "<b>diec</b>" will give you at least "Tammo tom <b>Diec</b>k" and "Alexander Grothen<b>diec</b>k".]]></label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="pi1_title">mathematiker</label>
			<label index="pi1_ow-intro">Die Fotosammlung des Mathematischen Forschungsinstitutes Oberwolfach enthält
				Fotografien von Mathematiker weltweit. Die Sammlung baut auf einer Spende von
				Prof. Konrad Jacobs (Erlangen) aus den 1950ern auf. Seit ca. 1998 werden
				außerdem alle Oberwolfach besuchenden Gruppen fotografiert und so die Sammlung
				fortgeführt.
			</label>
			<label index="pi1_gen-intro">Ziel dieses Projektes ist es, über jeden promovierten Mathematiker die
				folgenden Informationen
				zusammenzutragen:
				Name des Mathematikers; Name der Universität, die den Doktorgrad verliehen hat; Verleihungsjahr; Titel
				der
				Dissertation; Betreuer.
			</label>
			<label index="pi_search-hint"><![CDATA[<b>Suche</b>: Die Suche ist eine vorn und hinten trunkierte Suche, z.B. mit der Eingabe
						'<b>diec</b>' erhalten Sie mindestens 'Tammo tom <b>Diec</b>k' und 'Alexander
						Grothen<b>diec</b>k'.]]></label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
